# **Jakub Cichon**

West Hartford, CT 860 - 716 - 1713 jakub@uconn.edu jakubcic.github.io/portfolio/

## **Objective**

Skilled and highly technical System Administrator with 4+ years experience and recent Coding Bootcamp graduate with a passion for automation and impeccable attention to detail looking to transition to an early career position in software development that demands strong problem solving, analytical and troubleshooting skills and provides the opportunity to learn, grow and do my best work.

### Education

### University of Connecticut, Online

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp - September 2022 to March 2023

- Develop web applications using technologies like JavaScript + Node.js, React, MySQL, MongoDB, Heroku
- · Collaborate with small teams of classmates on projects, then present and demo our work

University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT

Bachelor of Arts, Statistics - May 6, 2018

· Major GPA: 3.84

## **Employment Experience**

## Connecticut Online Computer Center (COCC), Rocky Hill, CT

Middleware Technology Services Team, Web Infrastructure Specialist II — September 2018 to present

- Support the organization's largest product offerings to the financial industry, iBanking and INSIGHT, including maintenance, configuration, and deployment
- Maintain supporting applications for the iBanking product on both Windows Server and Linux (RHEL) infrastructure, including monitoring solutions and third party on-premises software as well as applications developed in-house
- Leverage tools like Ansible and scripting languages to automate processes and save the team significant time and reduce toil
- Develop command line tools and PowerShell modules to automate application deployment, service management, and application configuration
- Document our tools and applications
- · Lead internal informal learning sessions for my team
- Respond to and manage incidents while coordinating with teams across the organization
- · Participate in an on-call rotation and maintain availability for off-hours incidents

**University Information Technology Services**, University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT *Network Operations Center, Student IT Specialist (Full Time)* — May 2017 to August 2017

**University Information Technology Services**, University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT *Academic IT, Student IT Assistant (Part Time)* — September 2015 to May 2017

## Skills

Tools PowerShell, Bash, Ansible, git, GitLab CI/CD, Splunk, Heroku, Visual Studio Code

Web Development HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express, React, MySQL, MongoDB, Webpack, GraphQL

General Problem Solving, Technical Writing, Troubleshooting, Learning

## **Projects**

Mega Tech Blog, University of Connecticut Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

https://mega-tech-blog.herokuapp.com

- · Microblogging website with user auth and user generated content (posts and comments) built with the MVC paradigm
- · Node.is, Handlebars.is for templating, TailwindCSS, Express.is, MySQL

**GRIMS (General Retail Inventory Management System)**, University of Connecticut Full Stack Coding Bootcamp <a href="https://grims-inventory.herokuapp.com">https://grims-inventory.herokuapp.com</a>

- Online inventory manager demonstrating grocery departments and products built with the MVC paradigm
- Supports user authentication, password resets, adding, editing, and deleting products and cloud image hosting
- Node.js, Handlebars.js for templating, Bootstrap 5, Express.js, MySQL, Cloudinary SDK

Interests & Activities Tabletop Games, Movies, Ringer-Verse Podcast, Changelog Podcast, Ship It Podcast